<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">College App</string>
    <string name="regular" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/trebucbd</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="start">start</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="it">Information technology (IT) is the use of any computers, storage, networking and other physical devices, infrastructure and processes to create, process, store, secure and exchange all forms of electronic data. Typically, IT is used in the context of business operations, as opposed to technology used for personal or entertainment purposes. The commercial use of IT encompasses both computer technology and telecommunications. Information Technology means the use of hardware, software, services, and supporting infrastructure to manage and deliver information using voice, data, and video.</string>
    <string name="mech">mechanical engineering is the application of the principles and problem-solving techniques of engineering from design to manufacturing to the marketplace for any object. Mechanical engineers analyze their work using the principles of motion, energy, and force—ensuring that designs function safely, efficiently, and reliably, all at a competitive cost.Mechanical engineers make a difference. </string>
    <string name="entc">Electronics and Telecommunication Engineering is a well-known branch of engineering. It deals with the reception of video, microprocessors, analogue communication, digital and analogue integrated circuits, satellite communication, antennae and wave progression, solid-state devices, voice and data etc. It is a three-year long course having 6 semesters in it. Electronics and Telecommunication Engineering is a well-known branch of engineering. It deals with the reception of video.</string>
    <string name="cs">Computer engineers continually push the capability and applicability of computers in every industry and every facet of modern life. Computer engineers are concerned with analyzing and solving computer-oriented problems. CPEs understand both the hardware and the software of computers. This enables them to choose the solution that is best, not just the one they know. Sometimes the answer to making a program more efficient is a change in the computer itself.</string>
    <string name="about_clg">Progressive Education Society is a reputed and distinguished educational institution in Maharashtra. Progressive Education Society was established in year 1934 in Pune by Honorable, Late Shankarrao Kanitkar, along with his dedicated team of teachers known for the highest moral values.It was established by five prominent teachers and experts in the field of education. The motto of Progressive Education Society is "EVER TO EXCEL". The mission statement of Progressive Education Society is "Dnyanamayo Bhava" which is taken from Rigveda.P.E. Society has been making noteworthy progress for the last 78 years.There are in total 53 Educational Institutions (Ranging from Pre-Primary to Post-Graduation) imparting quality education. It has Distinguished Alumni of Eminent personalities as alumnus.The motto of Progressive Education Society is "EVER TO EXCEL". The mission statement of Progressive Education Society is "Dnyanamayo Bhava" which is taken from Rigveda.P.E. Society has been making noteworthy progress for the last 78 years.There are in total 53 Educational Institutions (Ranging from Pre-Primary to Post-Graduation) imparting quality education. It has Distinguished Alumni of Eminent personalities as alumnus.</string>
    <string name="about_clg2">The motto of Progressive Education Society is "EVER TO EXCEL". The mission statement of Progressive Education Society is "Dnyanamayo Bhava" which is taken from Rigveda.P.E. Society has been making noteworthy progress for the last 78 years.There are in total 53 Educational Institutions (Ranging from Pre-Primary to Post-Graduation) imparting quality education. It has Distinguished Alumni of Eminent personalities as alumnus.</string>
    <string name="about_clg3">In true sense, the activities of this society have always been Progressive and Modern. Inspired by the vision and goal and responsibility towards society, honorable Chairman Dr. G.R. Ekbote, accepted the challenge of providing education a real meaning and a new dimension to the society. The ambitious plan of Modern College of Engineering was initiated in the academic year 1999–2000.</string>
</resources>